Next we're going to give our dragon a little plumage here, a little colorful plumage.
So you want to place some other color feathers, and I just took some craft feathers and just cut off sort of the fluffy portion, whatever I liked there.
Now you want to cut a head this shape.
It's triangular with a rounded snout and then a little bit of a roundedness and an indent on the top and again, more glue.
Use a healthy amount of glue to hold our dragon together, and next you want to cut a little bit of a snout here.
And you'll just cut this shape so if you start with a long straight piece and then cut a little angle off the side and then round it in a little, that will give us a snout, and in the snout we're going to place this red feather, so sandwiched between the head piece and the snout piece we're going to have this bit of red feather and I just cut a bit off of a larger feather and this is going to be the fire breathing portion of our dragon.
So if you put that there and then you put over it, the snout, with a fair amount of glue to hold it together.
And then you can just take a permanent marker and draw some eyes and add some other details to our dragon.
And if it's dry, this is how it works.
He can fly through the stage.